A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor Joseph Johnson, 1852-1855
Library of Virginia
- Oversized (Newspaper Box)
  - 1854
    - Nov. 2 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - 1855
    - Jan. 25 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Mar. 13 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Apr. 11 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Apr. 14 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - May 24 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - May 24 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - June 29 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Undated